So, hello everyone, we have almost completed the backend section for this chat app.
So, as you can see that controller is library, middleware, model and routes have been made.
So now let's go to this navigate to the front and folder because now we are going to work
on that.
And for that we are going to install one important package which is called as Tailwind
CSS.
So, for installing the Tailwind CSS, what you can do is actually go to this site which
is Tailwind CSS slash docs, slash installation, slash using wheat.
And now just copy this line of code here as you can see and then just go back to your
VS code and just install this.
So, it's going to take some time.
So now basically we are going to do, we are going to just set up the front end of our app,
we are going to install such packages and we are going to work on that.
Now, since this tailwind is installed as you can see there, if you go in the front end folder
in the front end folder, you can see this wheat.config.js file right.
So now go back to this website again.
Now what you have to do is just a client of code, take this line of code and then just
go back to the VS code and add this one.
So control V, so control S to save it.
Now what you are going to do is you have to, in this plugin section, you have to also
add the plugins right.
So for that one, let's go here.
Now for this plugin part, control C and control V, just paste it there, okay.
So this one is also set up now, after this, we are going to just import this at the rate
of import tailwind, CSS and in the index.js folder, index dot, sorry, index dot, CSS folder.
So remove all of the pre-built things and just control S save.
Now the app would be running, okay.
So to run our app, so end dev, let's run our wheat application and see what's happening.
So to taking some time, meanwhile, one thing which you have to do is like all of these
pre-made template, as you can see, this is a counter app, okay.
So you have to remove all of these because we are going to work with our application.
So let's go here, so we will have 5173.
So now it's opening, our system is...
So as you can see that this wheat plus react site is open, okay.
So let's close this to and every move, the CSS, that's why it's looking like this.
So now this is the pre-made template, so all you can do is just remove all of this.
And also this const, count and set count, just remove all the div and we will have this
thing here, okay.
So in order to display that Tailwind is working efficiently, so let's return one something,
return H1 class name equals to suppose text green 300 and then suppose we just take this
as like type it as chat app, okay, chat app, okay.
Control as save, okay, there's some issue.
So for this return part, actually we have to remove this, okay, double return statements,
my bad.
Now let's run again, it's running fine, because you can see this chat app is currently
coming with this green text, okay.
So now we have set up our like basic wheat with Tailwind.
In the next section, we are going to install some packages and we are going to work with
it.
Thanks.